Guide to the William Sims papers, 1977-2003.
Sims, William papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
William Sims papers, 1977-2003.
23-16-3759
William. Sims
1 cubic foot.
Correspondence, Publications, Reports, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, publications, reports, course material, and subject files relating to Sims' work in facility management and designing workplaces.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor Emeritus in the Dept. of Design and Environmental Analysis, Cornell University.
Sims received a Bachelor of Architecture degree from the University of New Mexico in 1963, a Masters in Architecture degree from the University of Pennsylvania in 1965 and a PhD from MIT in 1974.
Sims was active in facility management education since his arrival at Cornell in 1980 and was co-director of the International Workplace Studies Program.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, publications, reports, course material, and subject files relating to Sims' work in facility management and designing workplaces.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Sims, William.; Cornell University--Faculty.; New York State College of Human Ecology.Dept. of Design and Environmental Analysis.
Subjects:
Facility management.; Office buildings.; Work environment--Design.; Quality of work life.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence, 1978 - 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Abstracts (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Articles and Papers by Sims, 1970s - 1980s (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Articles Where Sims is Cited, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Course Material From Ohio State, 1977 - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Course Material From Ohio State, 1979 - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Course Material From Cornell, 1981 - 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Short Course Slides (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Talks, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Presentations: Facility Planning and Management, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Presentation: ASTM Toronto, Late 1980s (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Presentations, 1986 - 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Presentation: Advisory Council, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Presentation: IFMA, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Conference: Alt.office - San Jose, CA, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Presentations: Overheads (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Presentations: IDRC (Box 1, Folder 17)
- "Managing the Reinvented Workplace" Overheads (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Certification: Overheads (Box 1, Folder 19)
- DEA Careers: Overheads (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Educational Objectives: Overheads (Box 1, Folder 21)
- International Facilities Management Research Project: Overheads (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Professional Development for Architecture: Overheads, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- DEA Mission and Interior Design: Overheads (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Flexible Workplace Strategies: Overheads (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Design Strategy Rating Modification Guide, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Research Study: Hatch U.S.D.A - Sims Principal Investigator (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Surveys: Organization and I, Building, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Space Cost Project, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Campus Planning Issues (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Accreditation Application for Interior Design Program, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Proposal to Establish a University Facilities Research Program, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Graduate Major in Facility Planning and Mangement, late 1980s (Box 1, Folder 33)